Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Public Affairs Department Records 1945-2000 (bulk 1959-1996) MS 3009-RG 19
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Radio/TV Publicity Office Files, 1974-1990; 220697; 2.5 Linear feet (3 record cartons)
  - Time: Man of the Year: 1989, 220725 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 4)
  - Time: Man of the Year: 1990, 220726 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 5)
  - Time: Mock Election, 1988; 220727 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 6)
  - Time: Mock Inaugural Ball, 1989; 220728 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 7)
  - Time: The Newstour, 1978-1981; 220729 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 8)
  - Time: Photograph Exhibit: Boston, 1990; 220730 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 9)
  - Time: Radio Projects, 1989; 220731 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 10)
  - Time: Republican Conventions, 1984-1988; 220732 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 11-13)
  - Time: Russia Issue, 1989; 220733 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 14)
  - Time: Special Issue: "American Best", 1986; 220734 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 15)
  - Time: Special Issue on Women, 1990; 220735 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 16-18)
  - Time: 60th Anniversary Issue, 1983; 220736 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 19)
  - Time: Video News Release, 1989; 220737 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 20)
  - Time: Washington Bureau Chief Party, 1989; 220738 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 21)
  - Time: WMCA Radio, 1983; 220739 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 22-23)
  - Time World Newsradio, 1984; 220740 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 24)
- Series IV. Corporate Community Relations Office Files, 1990-2000; 3 Linear feet (3 boxes)
  Corporate Community Relations Office Files include records on various public interest programs and projects conducted by Time Inc. including yearly overview reports and records on exhibitions.
  It's US: A Celebration of Who We Are in America Today was a traveling photographic exhibition with a related student essay contest, lectures and publications created by Time Inc. as part of a diversity project.
  According to the finding aid in the Archives of the Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, Songs of My People was a book project developed by D. Michael Cheers, Eric Easter, and Dudley M. Brooks, and had Time Warner Cable as a major sponsor. The project included a traveling exhibition, a music video, and a lecture series. Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Services was the domestic exhibition sponsor, and United States Information Agency was the international exhibition sponsor. The records in this series are primarily papers on the traveling exhibition, copies of related publications, and audiovisual of the music video. Unreformatted audiovisual material in the collection is not accessible.
  Organized alphabetically.
  - Community / Social Responsibility Reports, 1990-2000 (Offsite-box 3291, Folder 1-2)
  - It's US: A Celebration of Who We Are in America Today, 1993-1997 (Offsite-box 2302)
    Records include educational material; correspondence with Don Wise Designs and Stonesong Press; memoranda on photograph research, planning, concept clarification, project overview and costs; action plans; and promotional material. The folders called "Originals" contain materials distributed to participants including progress updates, press releases, the essay contest overview, and excerpts from contest winners. The records are primarily from Vice President of Corporate Community Relations Toni Fay.
    Audiovisual includes:
    1 videocassette (VHS) (67 min.): 1/2 in. On container: "Fratelli Group. Russell Senate Tapes 4, 5, 6. Haddow Communications. It's US. Panel Discussion. Arthur Schlesinger and Others. 11/29/95. TRT: 67:00."
    1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "NY1 News Special. "It's US"."
  - Songs of My People: Papers, 1990-1998 (Offsite-box 3291, Folder 3-29)
    Papers include records from the 1991 planning conference of the traveling exhibit, correspondence with the exhibition sponsors, lists of participating museums, brochures, exhibition guides, pins, press kits, and materials from the exhibitions venues in Australia, South Africa, and Washington, D.C. The folder on South Africa includes a brochure and photographs from a Michael Cheers workshop.
  - Songs of My People: Audiovisual and Publications, 1992-1994 (Offsite-box 2510)
    Records includes audiovisual material:
    1 videocassette (U-matic). On label: "'Exposing Hidden Windows,' Producer, Michael Cheers, New African Visions, Inc. (RT: 29:46) and the 'Songs of My People Music Video,' Executive Producers, Glenda Bryant and Monica Sutton (RT: 14:40) Total Runing Time: 45:00."
    1 video reel (C Format). On label: "New African Productions, Inc. Producer: Michael Cheers. 'Exposing Hidden Windows.' African American Photographers. TRT: 29:46. Dub Master. 1/8/92. Same Audio Both Ch's."
    1 video reel (C Format). On label: "Songs of My People. 14:39." On container: "Actual Music Video Master."
    2 videocassettes (VHS) (14 min., 39 sec). On label: "Songs of My People. African Americans: A Self-Portrait. Music Video Single."
- Series V. Chief Speechwriter Peter Quinn Files, 1972-2000; 221147; 9 Linear feet (9 record cartons)
  Corporate Public Affairs vice president Donald Wilson's files indicate that Peter Quinn took over for Bob Rackleff as Chief Speechwriter in 1981 and lists the position as part of Corporate Public Affairs. Wilson's files do not record when Rackleff became Chief Speechwriter or when Time Inc. created the position.
  Records includes background materials and research, presumably to write speeches, and final copies of speeches for executives throughout Time Inc. Speeches in the speech files may have been written by Peter Quinn or his predecessor Bob Rackleff.
  - Analysts Meeting, 1988; 221160 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting of Shareholders, 1987; 221161 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1972-1979; 225511 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 3)
  - Articles and Statements: Davidson, Ralph P., 1985; 225512 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 4)
  - Articles and Miscellaneous: Sutton, Kelso, undated; 225514 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 5)
  - Discs [RESTRICTED], 1986-1998; 229673 (Offsite-box 2124)
    Includes discs with a variety of names, departments, offices, subsidiaries and topics written on them.
    108 computer discs (floppy disk): 5 1/4 in.
    13 computer discs (floppy disk): 3 1/2 in.
  - Financial Analysts Meeting, 1987; 221162 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1984; 225515 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 7)
  - Grunwald, Henry, 1981-1987; 221163 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 8-9)
  - Levin, Gerald: "Values for the Digital Age: The Legacy of Henry Luce", 2000; 221164 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 10)
  - Lyford Cay Transcript (of Strategic Planning), 1985; 231326 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 1)
  - Merger: Time Warner, 1989; 221166 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 2-5)
  - Munro, J. Richard, 1985-1988; 231327 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 6)
  - New York Historical Records Advisory Board, 1986-1987; 221167 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 7-9)
  - News Releases: Quarterly Reports, 1985-1988; 225519 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters: Vital Speeches of the Day, 1987 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters: Winners & Sinners, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 2)
  - Nicholas, N. J. (Nick), 1986-1992; 221169 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 11-12)
  - Paramount's Bid for Time Inc., 1989; 221170 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 13)
  - Scripts, 1986-1987; 221173 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 14)
  - Speeches: General: 1985 October-1986 February, 1985-1986; 225395 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 15-19)
  - Speeches: General: 1986 March-1989 December, 1986-1989; 231334 (Offsite-box 1764)
  - Speeches: General: 1990 January-1996, 1990-1996; 225404 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 1-8)
  - Speeches: General: 1990 September-1991 July, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 3-13)
  - Speeches: General: 1991 September-1992 June, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 14-23)
  - Speeches: General: 1992 September-1993 June, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 24-33)
  - Speeches: Brack, Reginald K., 1987-1994; 225505 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 9)
  - Speeches: Britt, Glenn, 1988; 225506 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 10)
  - Speeches: Cathcart, Mel, 1992; 225507 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 11)
  - Speeches: Davidson, Ralph P., 1985-1987; 225508 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 12-14)
  - Speeches: Dingman, Michael, 1989-1990; 225509 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 15)
  - Speeches: Fuchs, Michael, 1988-1995; 225510 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 16)
  - Speeches: Hayes, Jim, 1987; 221176 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 17)
  - Speeches: Meigher, Christopher, 1986-1991; 221177 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 18)
  - Speeches: Miller, Robert L., 1985; 221178 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 19)
  - Speeches: Morgado, Robert J., 1991-1992; 221179 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 20)
  - Speeches: Munro, J. Richard: 1985 October-1986 April, 1985-1986; 225537 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 21-23)
  - Speeches: Munro, J. Richard: 1986 March-1989 June, 1988-1993; 225538 (Offsite-box 1924)
  - Speeches: Munro, J. Richard: 1989 September-1999, 1989-1999; 225539 (Offsite-box 1925)
  - Speeches: Outside Time Inc., 1984-1991; 221180 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Payson, Martin, 1992; 221181 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 2)
  - Speeches: Rackleff, Bob, 1980-1985; 221182 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 3-6)
  - Speeches: Ross, Courtney Sale, 1991-1992; 225540 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 7)
  - Speeches: Ross, Steven J., 1990-1991; 225541 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 8-9)
  - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso, 1985-1987; 225542 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 10)
  - Speeches: Thomas, Richard B., 1987; 225543 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 11)
  - Speeches: Wilson, Donald M., 1986-1996; 225544 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 12)
  - Strategy Dinner, 1986; 221183 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 13)
  - Time Inc.: Corporate Identity, Mission, and Strategy, 1984-1988; 221184 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 14-18)
  - Time-Life Books, 1983-1986; 221185 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 19)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1986-1990 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 34)
  - Volunteerism, 1987 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 35)
  - Whittle Communications, 1992 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 36)
  - Women, 1983-1988 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 37)
- Series VI. Special Events Manager Ann Bellows Files, 1963-1996 (bulk, 1995-1996); 1.5 Linear feet (3 boxes)
  These files were accompanied by a transfer form from Ann Bellows sending records on the 1996 Atlanta Summer Olympics, a 1995 newstour, and historical newstour materials to the Time Inc. Archives.
  The newstour files are similar to the newstour administrative files in the Time Publishing and Business Records, and the Olympics files are similar to those in Jelmir Lucas's files. Corporate Public Affairs may have taken over the arrangement of these events from Time Promotion and Public Affairs in later years.
  Older newstour materials that encompassed entire folders or binders were returned to the Time Promotion and Public Affairs files. Files containing assembled historical records remain here with Bellows's files. Newstour records include a briefing binder on the various locations; itineraries and agenda; lists of and biographies on participants; invoices and bills; and branded stationary and other printed material.
  Olympics contains her work coordinating Olympics tickets, travel, and accommodations for Time Inc. staff and corporate guests for the 1996 summer games in Atlanta when Time Inc. was a sponsor. The materials include lists of participants, the scheduled program, and branded material including a selection of pins.
  - Archives Transfer Form, 1996 (Offsite-box 2326, Folder 3)
  - Newstours: Newstour 1995 (Offsite-box 2326, Folder 4-19)
    This newstour traveled to Cuba, Lebanon, India, Vietnam, Russia, and Hong Kong.
  - Newstours: Newstour 1995 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
  - Newstours: Historical Material, 1963-1995 (Offsite-box 2326, Folder 20-24)
    While planning the 1995 newstour, Bellows collected material from earlier newstours such as prior descriptions and participant lists.
  - Olympics: Summer Olympics 1996 (Offsite-box 3290, Folder 8-14)
  - Olympics: Summer Olympics 1996 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
- Series VII. Time Life International/Corporate International Files on Exhibitions and Contests, 1959-1971; 3 Linear feet (3 boxes)
  The management of the offsite and traveling exhibitions and loans started with Ed Lumsden and Jim Alberse in the promotion office of Time Life International (TLI). TLI became Corporate International in 1968 with Alberse in the public affairs office continuing management along with his assistant Jeanne Kerr. By 1969, Corporate International no longer existed as a department, and Alberse and Kerr transferred to Corporate Public Affairs still overseeing the international exhibitions and loans.
  Exhibitions in this collection were shown internationally and were either organized by Time Inc. or included loans from its collection. Exhibitions were to promote Time Inc. and its publications on an international scale or to promote specific aspects such as a new international publication like Life South Pacific or Life Asia. These exhibitions were managed separately from those shown in the Reception Center or Exhibition Center in the Time & Life Building.
  Records include requests for photographs from Time Inc.'s collection; requests for rights to reproduce photographs taken by photographers working for Life to use in exhibitions; requests from the United States Information Agency (previously United States Information Service) for Time Life International to prepare exhibitions for it such as American Arts and Skills and the Shelburne Museum; memoranda and correspondence regarding installation and shipping; exhibition catalogs, guides, and brochures; news clippings; and some photographs of installed exhibits. The records are primarily from Jim Alberse and Jeanne Kerr with some from Ed Lumsden.
  Organized alphabetically by topic.
  - Exhibitions: Miscellaneous, 1965-1971 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 1)
    Includes Life photograph loans, proposal for exhibits to show at the Time and Life Building, and a request to use the Time Inc. 40th anniversary film
  - Exhibitions: Alfred Eisenstaedt, 1968 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 2)
    Includes audiovisual material.
    1 film reel; 16mm. On container: "Mr. O'Callaghan. Life/Time D. Jones. TV Channel 7 Brisbane. News Coverage '68. Eisenstadt exhibition."
    1 film reel; 16mm. (1 min., 12 sec). Label: "NLQ 539 Press Pix." On container: "Q'Land. Aust. B'Cast Commission Brisbane. T.V. News Film Coverage Eisenstadt Exhibition April 23, 1968."
  - Exhibitions: American Arts and Skills, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 3-4)
  - Exhibitions: American Arts and Skills [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R26)
  - Exhibitions: Eliot Elisofon, 1967 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 5)
    Loans of Elisofon's photographs for an exhibition in Japan.
  - Exhibitions: Gordon Parks, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 6-10)
    Loans of Parks's photographs for a traveling exhibition and for Photokina.
  - Exhibitions: Herald Tribune Photographs, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 11)
  - Exhibitions: Illuminations of Fifty Great Paintings, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 12-17)
    A traveling exhibition produced by Life.
  - Exhibitions: Illuminations of Fifty Great Paintings, circa 1959-1971 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 1-4)
  - Exhibitions: Paul Hogarth, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 5)
    Loan of Hogarth's photographs for an exhibition at the Royal College of Art in London.
  - Exhibitions: Sony Tokyo, 1966 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 6)
  - Exhibitions: Thirty Years of Life, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 7)
    Shown in Australia to promote Life South Pacific.
  - Exhibitions: Time Cover Art Show to Canada, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 8)
  - Exhibitions: Treasures from Poland, 1967 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 9)
    An exhibition that Time Inc. attempted to borrow through the American ambassador to Poland for the Time Inc. Exhibition Center.
  - Exhibitions: Shelburne Museum, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 10)
  - Life en Espaol Writing Contest: Prize Stories from Latin America, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 11)
  - Life en Espaol Writing Contest: Prize Stories from Latin America [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R26)
  - Life en Espaol Writing Contest: Secret Ceremony, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 12-14)
    Records are regarding an author's copyright concern involving a film based on a novel based on a story submitted to the contest.
  - Life en Espaol Writing Contest: Secret Ceremony, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 2326, Folder 1)
  - Life en Espaol Writing Contest: Secret Ceremony [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R26)
  - Life International, 1961?, undated (Offsite-box 2326, Folder 2)
    Includes a film roll of a possible presentation titled The Promise and Purpose of Life international version and audiovisual material.
    1 audiotape reel (BASF): analog, 7 1/2 ips; 3 in., 8 cm. tape. On container: "Radio Spot. Life International 25 sec JW 6006 Track 10."
- Series VIII. General Files, 1945-1999; 221830; 26.5 Linear feet (26 boxes, 35 reels of microfilm)
  Corporate Public Affairs General Files include annual reports, press releases, dinner books, weekly news clippings, and administrative files. General Files refer to all Corporate Public Affairs records that were not clearly created by or transfered by one office or individual. Some items in the first four subseries may include an individual's name, usually James Pitt, Louis Slovinsky or Stan Kapner. Some materials are to and from Jeanne Kerr, initially a public affairs assistant and later director of corporate contributions.
  Organized into six subseries:
  Subseries VIII.A. Administrative Files
  Subseries VIII.B. Annual Reports
  Subseries VIII.C. Dinner Books
  Subseries VIII.D. Press Releases
  Subseries VIII.E. Scrapbooks
  Subseries VIII.F. Weekly News Clippings
  - Subseries VIII.A. Administrative Files, 1963-1989; 221729; 18 Linear feet (18 boxes)
    Administrative Files include material to educate Corporate Public Affairs on Time Inc. activities and to assist staff on writing press releases and other communications regarding the activities. Records include financial and security analyst meeting agenda; briefing books, president's speeches, photographs, and questions and answers for the stockholders' annual meetings; background information and progress updates on joint ventures; background information, fact sheets, and press releases on Time Inc. publications, public programs, and departments; magazine media and advertising kits; and news clippings.
    The administrative files are primarily from Slovinsky, but also include files or materials from Donald Wilson, Kerr, Pitt, Kapner, public affairs senior associate Ed Adler, and press information manager Michael Luftman. These files may have been inherited by Slovinsky, filed together by an office worker in Corporate Public Affairs prior to transfer to the Time Inc. Archives, or filed together by the Time Inc. Archives after receipt. For example, earlier Analyst Meeting and Stockholder Meeting files from Pitt were housed with later similarly titled files from Slovinsky. While the speeches folders have material similar to the Chief Speechwriter series, this material looks like it was collected by Slovinsky or a different part of Corporate Public Affairs and not the Chief Speechwriter.
    Items of interest include a 1970 plan for pre-recorded video; a 1972 title list for Time-Life Video; photographs of a 1972 stockholders meeting; and a collection of letters from a campaign by the striking workers of the International Paper Androscoggin Mill in Maine.
    Unreformatted audiovisual and digital material in the collection is not accessible.
    - Advertising Age: 100 Leading Advertisers, 1981-1988; 229556 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 1-8)
    - Adweek, 1981-1982; 229565 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 9)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Graphic Standards Manual, 1986; 221734 (Offsite-box 1749, Folder 8)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Knickerbocker Communications: General, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 13-14)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Knickerbocker Communications: Franchise Proposal, 1980 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 15)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Knickerbocker Communications: Queens Franchise, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 16)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Releases, 1977-1986 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 1-5)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Slides, undated (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 6)
    - Analysts Meetings, 1965-1971; 221738 (Offsite-box 1749, Folder 9-16)
    - Analysts Meetings, 1974-1985; 221740 (Offsite-box 1750, Folder 1-12)
    - Analysts Presentations, 1964-1980; 221741 (Offsite-box 1750, Folder 13-14)
    - Analysts Reports, 1970-1982; 221742 (Offsite-box 1750, Folder 15-21)
    - Analysts Reports, 1983-1987; 221744 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 1-6)
    - Annual Meeting, 1986 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 1-4)
      "Original Q&A" folder includes digital material:
      1 computer disc (floppy disk): 8 in.
    - Annual Meeting, 1987 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 5-10)
      "Q&As Originals" folder includes digital material:
    - Annual Meeting, 1988 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1963; 221745 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 7-8)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club Newsletter: At Our Club, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 12)
    - Broadcast, 1969-1973; 221746 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 9-10)
    - Cable, 1980-1984; 221747 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 11)
    - Cable TV Advertising, 1980; 221748 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 12)
    - CBS/Time Inc. Age Wave, 1989; 229566 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 10)
    - Changes and Choices in Employee Benefits, 1987; 229567 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 11)
    - Chicago: Building and Cover Show, 1978-1984 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 13)
    - Chicago: Relocation: Books and Magazine/AFP Operations, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 14)
    - Corporate Aircraft, 1977 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 15)
    - Corporate Articles: Examples of Time Inc. Magazines Cirticizing Time Inc. Products, 1987 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 16)
    - Corporate Cultural Affairs News, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 17)
    - Corporate History: 1975-Present, 1985 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 18)
    - Covering Note and Order Form for Annual Report, 1981; 229568 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 12)
    - Covidea: General, 1985; 221750 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 13-14)
      Covidea files contain material on a joint venture between Time Inc., AT&T, Bank of America, and Chemical Bank.
    - Covidea: Background Material, 1985; 221752 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 15-16)
    - Covidea: Conference Calls of Communications Committee, 1985; 221753 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 17)
    - Covidea: Heffron, Frank, 1985; 221774 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 1)
    - Covidea: News Release Announcement, 1985-1986; 221775 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 2)
    - Covidea: Q&A Development, 1985; 221776 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 3)
    - Dallas Morning News, 1987 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 1)
    - Direct Broadcast Satellite TV, 1983-1984; 221777 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 4)
    - Earnings: 1981: Press Releases, 229569 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 13-20)
    - Earnings: 1981: Proxy Statement, 229570 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 21)
    - Earnings: 1981: Reports to Shareholders, 229571 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 22-24)
    - Earnings: 1982: Letter to Shareholders, 229572 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 25)
    - Earnings: 1982: Press Releases, 229573 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 26-34)
    - Earnings: 1982: Proxy Statement, 229574 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 35)
    - Earnings: 1982: Reports to Shareholders, 229575 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 36-38)
    - Edit Seminar, 1978 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Invest in MGM, 1967; 221778 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 5)